We're running low on resumes.
瑞秋,履历表已用完了
You want a job with Popular Mechanics?
你真想到“大众技工”上班吗?
If you're gonna work for mechanics, those are the ones.
如果你真想为技工工作 那儿倒儿可试试
Guys,I'm going for anything here. I can't be a waitress anymore.
各位,我什么都得试试 我不能再当服务生了
I'm sick of the lousy tips. I'm sick of being called "Excuse Me."
我是说真的我已厌倦微薄小费 我已厌倦别人对我说“麻烦一下”
-Paper cut! Paper cut! -Here.
-裁纸刀!裁纸刀! -这里
Grapefruit juice! Grapefruit juice!
柚子汁!柚子汁!
Okay,we're almost done. Only 20 more to go.
差不多搞定了.只剩20份了
-Rach,did you proofread these? -Yeah. Why?
-瑞秋,这些你已校对过? -对,有问题吗?
Nothing. I'm sure they'll be impressed with your "compuper" skills.
没事,他们对你的“垫脑”技巧一定会印象深刻的
Oh,my God! Do you think it's on all of them?
糟了,每一份上面都这样吗?
No,I'm sure the Xerox machine caught a few.
没有,影印机弄掉一些了
The One With the Poker
六人行 第1季 第18集 玩扑克
-=BT之家DRM小组 http://bbs.btbbt.com=- 荣誉出品 河马根据网络字幕微调制作
They call this a love seat but I'm not feeling anything special towards you.
他们把这里叫做情侣座. 可是和你对面一点感觉都没有
-Hey,guys. -Hey.
-嗨,小伙子们 -嗨
Hi,ladies.
嗨,小姐们
Can I get you anything? Did you bring the mail?
需要什么吗?信件带来了没?
-Lots of responses. -Really? Sure,we have scones left!
-很多回复 -当然?我们这儿当然有烤饼
Read them.
快念给我听
"Dear Miss Greene: Thank you for your inquiry. However"
亲爱的格林小姐感谢您的询问,然而…
-We have apple cinnamon -"Dear Ms. Greene...." Yeah,yeah! No.
-我们有苹果肉桂…-亲爱的格林小姐…好，好，不行.
-What? -Your Visa bill is huge!
-怎么了?-你的开销不小呀
Give me that.
给我
Linda's great. Why won't you go out with her?
我真不敢相信 琳达那么好你为何不再和她约会?
-I don't know. -ls this about her...
-我也不知道 -是因为她说了
... "The Flintstones could have really happened" thing?
石头族真有可能发生?
It's not just that. I want someone who does something for me...
不只是因为那样 因为我要一个能让我有感觉
...who gets my heart pounding.
能让我心跳加速
Who makes me....
让我…
Little playthings with yarn?
感情经验丰富的女人
What?
什么?
Could you want her more?
你不是渴望着她?
Who?
谁?
Dee,the sarcastic sister from What's Happening!!.
明蒂,《发生何事》中 那个尖酸刻薄的女孩
Look,I'm totally over her.
我早就忘了她,行吗?
-Hi! -Coffee?
-好啊! -咖啡?
-No,we're fine. -Okay.
-我们很好 -好的
-Shut up! -We're not saying anything.
-闭嘴! -我们什么都没说
-What? -Joey cried last night.
-什么? -昨晚乔伊哭了
-Thank you. -We were playing poker
-谢谢 -我们正在玩扑克牌
There was chocolate on the three. It looked like an eight.
三点上有巧克力看起来像是八点
You should have seen him. "Read them and weep!"
可惜你没看到 他说“准备痛哭流涕吧”
And then he did.
结果哭的是他
Now,how come you guys have never played poker with us?
你们怎么没和我们玩过扑克牌?
Yeah,what is that? Like some kind of sexist guy thing?
对,为什么? 好像这是有性别歧视的男人的专利
-It's poker,so only guys can play? -No. Women can play.
-这是扑克,只有男人才玩?  -才怪,女生也欢迎加人
Then,what is it? Some kind of,like, some kind of,you know
那么为什么…这样的一些,为什么
All right,what is it?
到底为什么?
There are just no women in our game.
只是刚好女生没加入罢了
We just don't know any women who know how to play poker.
对,我们刚好找不到会玩的女生
That is a lame excuse. It's a typical guy response.
拜托,这个借口真烂 男生都是这种反应
Do you know how to play?
请问你们谁会玩扑克牌?
No.
不会
-But you could teach us. -No.
-你们可以教我 -不要
Okay,so now we draw cards.
现在开始抽牌
So I wouldn't need any. I have a straight.
我不需要换牌对吧? 因为我一把顺
-Oh,good for you! -Congratulations!
-对你来说不错! -恭喜了!
-Pheebs,how many do you want? -I just need two.
-菲比,你要几张? -我需要两张
The 10 of spades and the 6 of clubs.
黑桃十和梅花六
-No,you can't -I have the 10 of spades! Here.
-不,你不能那样做 -等等,我有你要的黑桃
Thanks!
谢谢!
-No,you can't do that. -Don't need them. I'm going for fours.
-不…不能那样 -不…可以,我不需要.我要四张同点
Oh,you're
哦,你们
You're going for fours. Chandler,could you? Thanks,man.
我要四张同点.钱德, 你有吗?谢谢,小伙
Here we go.
开始吧
We've got salmon roulettes and crudites.
我们有鲑鱼乐透和水果盘
What are you doing?
摩妮卡,你在干什么?
In poker,there's no food with more than one syllable.
扑克里面,食物的名称不能超过一个音节
It's got to be like chips or dip or pretz
洋芋片,沙司,椒盐卷…
I hope you'll let it slide just this once. I was all out of "pretz."
我希望你能只卷这一次
Now the dealer
现在开始发牌
We got it. Let's play for real. High stakes. Big bucks!
知道了.开始玩真的吧.高赌资,大笔钱
You sure? Phoebe just threw away two jacks because they didn't look happy.
你当真?菲比刚丢出十一点(杰克) 因为他们好像不开心
But I'm ready. So just deal.
我准备好了,发牌
Okay,last-minute lesson! Joey....
各位,最后通知!乔伊有
Three.
三点
Eight.
八点
Eight. Three. All right,very good.
八点,三点,好的,不错
Damn it,damn it,damn it!
该死,该死,该死!
Joey had two fives showing, so for you to raise was
乔伊面上又一对5,该你们叫牌
Yes?
好的?
Downright gutsy.
明显而且大胆
-I see,so you were lying. -About what?
-我明白,就是骗 -骗什么?
-About how good your cards were. -I was bluffing.
-骗你们牌有多好 -我在唬你们
And what is bluffing?
什么是唬?
Is it not another word for lying?
不就是骗的同义字吗?
Sorry to break up this party,but I've got to go fax resumes before work.
抱歉,我不能再玩了 我在明天工作前得打好履历表
-We've got to settle. -Settle what?
-瑞秋,我们得算帐(定居) -什么定居?
The Jamestown colony of Virginia.
在维吉尼亚的詹姆斯城殖民地
See,King George is giving us the land....
乔治王把土地给我所以…
-The game,Rachel. You owe us money. -Right.
-瑞秋,是赌局,你欠我们钱 -哦,好
It's their first time. Let's forget about the money.
你们知道吗?这是她们的第一次 别和她们计较钱了
Hell,no. We'll pay!
不好,我们会付钱的
Monica,I had another answer all ready.
摩妮卡,我有另一个答案了
And you know what? We want a rematch.
知道吗?我们要再来一次
That's fine with me. Could use some money.
不错,我有钱花了
-You're enjoying this,aren't you? -Well,yeah,I am.
-你很享受这个,是不是 -我想是的
So you get your ya-yas by taking money from your friends.
这么说你们的组合家俱 都用朋友的钱买来的
Yes,and I get my ya-yas from KEA.
没错,而且我是在“宜家家俱”买的
You have to put them together yourself,but they cost less.
自己得动手装,便宜许多
Look,this is poker. I play to win.
瑞秋,这是扑克牌,玩就是要赢
For me to win, others have to lose.
为使我能赚钱别人就得输
If you're gonna play, don't expect me to be nice.
如果想和我玩牌就别指望我手下留情
Because once those cards are dealt....
因为牌一发出
Yeah?
然后呢?
I'm not a nice guy.
我就六亲不认
All right,let's eat.
各位,吃吧
Did you get that from the "I Love Rachel Pizzeria"?
这是从“我爱瑞秋匹萨屋”买的吗?
-You still on that? -What was with that Black Bart speech?
-你们还在取笑我? -别这样嘛,为何学起黑道
"When I play poker, I'm not a nice guy."
玩起牌来我六亲不认
You're way off.
你扯太远了
No,I don't think so, because I think you love her!
我可不这么认为 因为我认为你爱她
No. I might have had feelings for her at one time. Not anymore.
不,或许我曾过她有意思 爱意早已消失
I just
我只是
Marcel! Where are you going with that disk?
马修!你想把CD片怎么了?
You are not putting that on again.
不能再放上去,马修
If you press that button, you are in very big trouble.
如果你们再闹,你可真的有大麻烦了
You believe what a jerk Ross was being?
你知道罗斯那混蛋有多烂吗?
-Yeah,I know. -He can get really competitive.
-我懂 -他的好胜心最强了
What?
什么?
"Hello,kettle? This is Monica. You're black!"
凯蒂,我是摩妮卡,你是黑人
Please!
拜托
I'm not as bad as Ross.
我没像罗斯那么烂
I beg to differ. The Pictionary incident?
我抗议,“字典”事件呢?
That wasn't an incident.
我不是故意的
I was gesturing and the plate slipped out of my hand.
我在做手势时盘子不慎滑落
-I got an interview! -You're kidding! Where?
-他们叫我去面谈了! -你在开玩笑吧?哪儿?
Saks Fifth Avenue.
第五大道萨克斯
Oh,Rachel!
哦,瑞秋
It's like the mother ship is calling you home.
这就像是母船叫你归队
-What's the job? -Assistant buyer.
-是什么工作? -采购助理
I would be shopping!
我要用购物…
For a living!
来谋生了
That's Aunt lris. She's been playing poker since she was 5.
她叫艾莉丝姑姑 她从五岁起便开始玩牌
You've got to listen to every word she says.
她说的每字我们都得牢记在心
-ls Tony Randall dead? -I don't think so.
-东尼蓝道死了? -我看不是
-He may be now. I hit him with my car. -My God,really?
-现在可能已死因为我开车撞到他了 -天啊…真的?
No,that's bluffing. Lesson number one.
不,唬你们的,第一课
Let me tell you something. Everything you hear at a poker game is pure crap!
告诉你们玩牌听到的每个字都是狗屁
-Nice earrings. -Thank you.
-不错的耳环 -谢…
-Girls,sit down. -Aunt lris,this is Phoebe and Rachel.
-坐吧,各位 -艾莉丝姑姑,这位是菲比,她叫瑞秋
Listen,I'm parked at a meter. Let's do it. Okay?
我的车停在计时器前,开始吧
We'll start with five-card draw.
我们从抽五张牌开始
Then we'll go into the studs and the hold 'ems. I talked to Cousin Nathan.
然后我们开始看牌并且持牌. 我跟南希堂兄说
Don't touch the cards when somebody is dealing.
发牌的时候不要碰牌
How is Nathan?
南希怎么样?
Now he thinks he's a man in a woman's body.
他现在以为他是一个在女人身体里的男人
Don't you mean a woman in a man's body?
你是说一个女人在男人的身体里?
It should be so simple.
这很简单是吧
Ross,could we please listen to anything else?
罗斯,我们能听点别的吗?
All right.
好吧
I'm gonna pay for that tonight.
我今晚可要倒大楣了
Hi. Guys,guess what?
嗨,伙计们,猜猜看?
The fifth dentist caved,and now they're all recommending Trident?
第五位牙医投奔他们,推荐“三叉戟”?
No,the interview!
不,是面谈
Unbelievable! She absolutely loved me.
简直无法相信!她喜欢我
We talked for over two hours. We've the same taste in clothes.
我们谈了两个半小时 我们对服饰的品味一致
And I went to camp with her cousin.
我从前还和她的表妹一起去过夏令营
-The job is perfect! I can do this. -That's great!
-这工作简直是太棒了,我可以胜任 -太好了…
-Then she told a funny story. -Great,tell us and we'll laugh.
-然后她告诉我最好笑的事 -很好,你讲时我们一定会笑
Let's play poker!
玩牌吧
Listen,we talked about it and if you don't wanna play,it's okay.
各位听好,我们谈过此事 如果你想不玩我们完全了解
Yes,we can play some other game. Like Pictionary?
对,我们可以玩别的像“字典”之类的
Very funny.
真好笑
-But we'd like to try poker again. -Yes,I think we should.
-我们想再给扑克牌一次机会 -我想是的
-Do you want me to shuffle those? -That's okay,I'm gonna give it a go.
-瑞秋,需要我来洗牌吗? -不用了,我想自己试试
So Pheebs owes $7. 50. Monica owes $10.00.
菲比欠7块5,摩妮卡欠10块
And Rachel,you owe 1 5 big ones!
瑞秋,你欠15块!
Thanks for teaching us Cross-Eyed Mary. We gotta play that other way.
谢谢教我们“斜眼玛丽” 我们该用另一种方式玩了
All right,here's my $7.50. But this money is cursed.
这是我的7块5,不过这钱已受到诅咒
-What? -I cursed it!
-什么? -我已对它下咒!
Now bad things will happen to the spender.
花这些钱的人会倒大楣
I'll take it. Bad things happen to me anyway.
无所谓,我接受.我反正够楣的了
This way,I can split them up with a movie.
这样我才能看场电影喘口气
So that just leaves the big Greene poker machine,who owes 1 5.
才刚离开绿色扑克牌机,谁就欠了15块
Could you be any smugger?
你能不能不打劫呢?
Let's see. Rach,I'm opening up a new art gallery...
让我看看.瑞秋,我准备开一个画廊
...and I could sure use the portraits of Lincoln and Hamilton.
我肯定可以用林肯和汉密尔顿的肖像
It's so typical. "I'm a man! I have a penis!
男生都这副德行 我是男人我有大家伙
I have to win money to exert my power over women!"
我得赢钱增加力量以征服女人
This isn't over.
知道吗?还没结束
We'll play you again. We'll win. You'll lose.
我们会再找你们玩 而且我们会赢你们会输
You'll beg. We'll laugh.
你们会祈求,我们会大笑
We'll take every last dime you have. And you'll hate yourselves forever!
我们会赢走你们的每一分钱 你们会永远恨死自己
Kind of stepped on my point there,Mon.
我们的意见一致,摩妮卡
I can't believe you lost! How much did they take?
我无法相信你输了!有多少?
Like 30 bucks.
差不多30块
-I'll give you that money back. -Really?
-我会把钱退回去的 -真的吗?
No,I'm bluffing! You guys haven't learned crap!
不,我在唬你!你们还没有学偷鸡!
-Hand me the cards! -Can l?
-把牌递给我! -我来行吗?
Yes!
是的!
Wanna give us your money now? We can skip the formality of really playing.
现在可以交出钱来吗? 如此我们就不必正式玩了
No,that's fine. We'll see who has the last laugh,monkey boy.
不,我倒要看看谁笑到最后,猴子男
Done with chitchat? Ready for serious poker?
聊完了没?可以开始玩真的没?
You guys,look! The one-eyed jack follows me wherever I go.
你们看,独眼杰克到处跟踪我
Right. Serious poker.
好,玩真的
-Mon,got any more of those salmon? -You want to eat or play poker?
-摩尼卡,你还有三文鱼吗? -你到底是吃东西还是玩牌?
-Where are you going? -To the bathroom.
-你要上哪儿去? -浴室
Want to go to the bathroom or play poker?
你想上厕所还是玩牌?
Go to the bathroom.
我想上厕所
-Well,I'm gonna order a pizza. -No!
-好吧,我去订此萨 -不
I'm waiting to hear from that job. The store closes at 9:00. Eat then.
我仍等着工作的电话通知 他们的店在9点关门那时候再吃吧
That's fine. I'll just have a Tic Tac to hold me over.
行,我含薄荷糖提神
All right. Cincinnati. No blinds. Everybody,ante.
未见牌不得下注,下注吧
Yes!
下…
Or no.
不下
-All right! Your money's mine,Greene. -Your fly's open,Geller.
-你的钱是我的了,菜鸟 -你的拉链没拉上,盖勒
You know what I just realized? Joker is poker with a "J"!
我刚刚才了解到,十一点上有个J
Coincidence?
真巧?
That's jo-incidence with a "C"!
那是J碰巧和一个C在一起
-Phoebe? -Yeah,I'm out.
-菲比? -我不跟了
-I'm in. -Me too.
-我跟 -我也跟
Me too. What do you got?
我也跟,你拿什么牌?
You better hop out of the shower, because I got a flush.
你最好逃出浴室 因为我拿五张同花(冲马桶)
Well,well,well!
好的,好的,好的!
Hop back in,bucko, because I got four sixes!
回来吧,小子,因为我拿了四张六
I got four sixes! I won! I actually won! Oh,my God!
我有四张六!我赢了… 我真的赢了,天哪
You know what? I'll make a little Ross pile.
你们知道吗?我要把小罗斯堆起来
Look!
看!
I think that one was Ross'. And I think that one was Ross'.
我想这是罗斯的 那个也是罗斯的
Well,I have got your money And you'll never see it
我赚到你的钱,你再无法见到它
And your fly's still open
你的拉链依然没拉上
I made you look
我让你低头看了
-I'm in. -I couldn't be in-er.
-我跟 -我不能跟
Monica,in or out?
摩妮卡,跟还不跟?
I hate this game!
我讨厌玩牌
Joey,your bet.
乔依,你呢?
I fold like a hooker who got hit in the stomach...
我像是被满脸伤痕的胖子
... by a fat guy with sores on his face.
撞到肚子的二流妓女
I'm out.
我不跟
-Ross? -I'm very in.
-罗斯? -我跟
-Chandler? -Couldn't be more out.
-钱德? -不跟
Me too. Rachel?
我也一样,瑞秋?
I will see you and I'll raise you. Do you wanna waste another buck?
我不但跟而且还要加注 如何?还想再浪费钱吗?
No,not this time. What did you have?
这一回不会.快嘛,给我看
-I'm not telling. -Show them.
-我不会说的 -给我看
-No. -Show them!
-不 -给我看
-Get your hands out of there! -I've had dates like this.
-把你的手从那里拿开! -我有同样的约会经验
Boy,you really can't stand to lose,can you?
天啊,你真是输不起的家伙
Your whole face is getting red. Veins popping out of your temple!
你的脸涨得好红 太阳穴的小血管都浮出来了
Plus,that shirt doesn't really match those pants.
而且衣裤并不相称
-I'm not losing. -You're definitely losing.
-第一,我没输 -别再谈输了,快发牌吧你输定了
Hello. Rachel Greene.
瑞秋格林
Excuse me. It's about the job!
这是有关工作的电话
Barbara,hi! How are you?
芭芭拉,你好吗?
No,I understand.
不,我懂
Come on. No,I'm fine. Don't be silly. Yeah.
不,我没事,快别这么说
But if anything else opens up,please
是否还有其他职缺请人?
Hello?
你好?
Sorry,Rach.
我很遗憾,瑞秋
There's gonna be lots of other stuff.
工作满街都是
Okay.
好的
Where were we?
Where were we? 玩到哪儿了?
Five-card draw. Jacks are better. Nothing wild. Everybody,ante.
拿五张牌,十一点比较好,大家下注
-Look,Rach,we don't have to do this. -Yes,we do.
-瑞秋,别再玩了 -要玩,下注
-All right. Check. -Check.
-好吧,下注 -下注
-I'm in for 50 cents. -Call.
-我下5毛钱 -跟跟
I'm in.
我跟
I see your 50 cents...
我跟你5毛
...and I raise you $5.
而且我要加5块钱
I thought it was a 50-cent limit.
我以为5毛是上限
I just lost a job, I'd like to raise it $5.
我刚失去工作所以想加5块
Does anyone have a problem with that?
各位有问题吗?
-Not at all. -No.
-当然没有 -没有
Loser?
输家?
-No,I fold. -What do you mean,you fold?
-退出 -退出是什么意思?怎么了?
I thought that,"Once the cards are dealt,I'm not a nice guy."
你不是发牌后就六亲不认的狠角色吗?
Were you just full of it?
还是只是虚张声势?
I'm in.
我跟
-How many do you want? -One.
-几张牌? -一张
Dealer takes two.
庄家两张
-What do you bet? -I bet $2.
-下多少? -我下2块
Okay. I see your $2...
我跟你2块
...and I raise you...
再加你
... 20.
20块
I see your $20...
我跟你20块
... raise you $25.
再加到25块
I see your $25 and Monica,get my purse.
跟你25块,摩妮卡,拿我的皮包来
Rachel,there's nothing in it.
瑞秋,里面没钱
Okay,then get me your purse.
那就拿你的皮包来
-Here you go. Good luck! -Thank you.
-给你.祝你好运! -谢谢
I saw your $25 and I raise you...
谢谢,跟你25块,再加
...seven.
…7块
teen!
10块!
Joey,I'm a little shy.
乔伊,我有点不好意思
That's okay,Ross. You can ask me.
没问题,你有什么问题可以问我
-What do you need? -1 5.
-要多少? -15块
-Here's 10. -I got 5.
-这里有10块 -我这里有5块
-Thank you. -Good luck.
-谢谢 -好运气
I am calling your 1 7.
再加十七块
What do you got?
你拿什么牌?
Full house.
葫芦
You got me.
败给你了
-That's tough to beat. -I thought we had it!
-那确实很难赢 -我因为我们会赢!
When you don't have the cards, you don't have the cards.
没有好牌就是没有好牌
But look how happy she is.
瞧,她多开心
-Airmail. -Airplane. Airport. Airport '75!
-航空邮件 -飞机.机场,机场75
Airport '77! Airport '79!
机场77,机场79
Time's up!
时间到
Bye Bye Birdie!
再见…小鸟
That's a bird?
那是小鸟?
That's a bird!
那就是小鸟!
Okay,it's my turn.
该我了
Go!
开始
Bean! Bean!
豆子!豆子!
The Unbearable Lightness of Being!
生命中无法承受的轻
That you get?
答对了
That you get?!
这样就能猜中…